A:
    rewrite:
    retrieval:
        history: 3
        question: "Question"
        model_answer: "Model_anwer"
B:
    rewrite:
        history: 5
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer: "Model_anwer"
    retrieval:
        history: 5
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer: "Model_anwer"
C:
    rewrite:
        history: 5
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer: "Model_anwer"
    retrieval:
        history: 1
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer:
D:
    rewrite:
        history: 5
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer: "Model_anwer"
    retrieval:
        history: 1
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer:
E:
    rewrite:
        history: 5
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer: "Model_anwer"
    retrieval:
        history: 1
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer:
F:
    rewrite:
        history: 0
        question: "Question"
        model_answer:
    retrieval:
        history: 1
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer:
G:
    rewrite:
        history: 0
        question: "Question"
        model_answer: "Model_anwer"
    retrieval:
        history: 1
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer:
H:
    rewrite:
        history: 0
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer:
    retrieval:
        history: 1
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer:
I:
    rewrite:
        history: 0
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer: "Model_anwer"
    retrieval:
        history: 1
        question: "Model_rewrite"
        model_answer:
